Guide to the Fernando Alegria Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 5. Notebooks
  - Inedito: Cantata: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Instrucciones original: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; yellow boards (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Latin America: the order of chaos: was it ever order?: notepad, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Literature Cubana: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Los de abajo: notes, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Made in USA I: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; grey boards (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Made in USA II: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; grey boards (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Made in USA III: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown boards (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Mañana los guerreros, no. 1: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Mañana los guerreros, no. 2: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Mañana los guerreros, no. 3: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Mañana los guerreros, no. 4: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Mañana los guerreros, no. 5: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; yellow boards (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Mañana los guerreros, no. 6: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; light blue boards (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Monjitas: notes, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Narrativa Mexicana de hoy: published volume, heavily annotated, with numerous notes tipped in (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Las noches del cazador: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown boards (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Notas: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; black boards (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Notas sobre El Che & Gabriel Mistral "Muerte del mar": notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Novela: revisiones, agregados: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Nueva Narrativa Latino Americana: notes & outlines, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Para un antologia del cuento norteamericano: notepad, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Los partidos "populares" en Chile: notepad, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Personal directory: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; boards loose (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Picasso: notes, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Picasso y Neruda seminario: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Poems: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; tan boards (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - El poeta que se transformó en gusano: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown boards (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Politica: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown boards (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Political statements related to Chile in Canto General: notes, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Rafael Arevalo Martinez: notes, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Revista Chilena -- Notas sueltos -- Pluma y lapiz -- Los X: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; tan boards (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Santiago del Nuevo extremo: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; black boards (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - The Sheridan circle: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Sociology and literature: notebook, ca. 1973, 1 v.; green boards (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Teatro: notepad, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Victorio I: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Voces del mando -- El ultimo general: notepad, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; black boards (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue-grey boards (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; light blue boards + 3 p. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Includes Juan Pablo II en Chile: tms, n.d -- 3 p.
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; orange boards (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red & white boards (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; tan boards (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; yellow boards (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Record book, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - En cuenta corriente con la Caja Nacional de Ahorros: notes written in savings passbook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Bluebook, 1941 Apr. 9, 1 v.; blue cover (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - [Unidentified], no. 3: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown cover (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - [Unidentified], no. 4: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown cover (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - [Unidentified], no. 5: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown cover (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - [Unidentified], no. 6: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown cover (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - [Unidentified], no. 7: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown cover (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - [Unidentified], no. 7: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; grey cover (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 205-217, n.d., 1 v.; tan cover (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 269-314, n.d., 1 v.; tan cover (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue cover (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 34a-37a, 56-82, n.d., 1 v.; red cover (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 83-101, n.d., 1 v.; yellow cover (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 83-101, n.d., 1 v.; yellow cover (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 102-107, n.d., 1 v.; brown cover (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 108-150, n.d., 1 v.; black cover (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 10-69, n.d., 1 v.; black cover (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 70-83, n.d., 1 v.; green cover (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Untitled notebook: pp. 84-110, n.d., 1 v.; orange cover (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Notepad, n.d., 1 item; yellow cover (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Notepad, n.d., 1 item; blue cover (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Notepad, n.d. Oct. 1, 1 item; lavendar cover (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Notepad, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Untitled notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown cover (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Notes on Jean Molino n.d. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Notas: La epica Romanticismo n.d. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Notas: Benedetti, Roa, Maifuez, etc. n.d. (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Notas para un ensayo sobre J.R. Romero n.d. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Notas: Pedro [?], La Voragine, Carpentier, Rayuelo n.d. (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Untitled notes, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Untitled notes, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Untitled notes, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Untitled notes, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous note cards, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Poesia chilena: bibliografia: note cards in wooden card box, n.d. (Box 61)
  - Poesia chilena: bibliografia: note cards in blue card box, n.d. (Box 61)
  - Fernando Alegria: Bibliografía cronologica: note cards, n.d. (Box 61)
  - Walt Whitman bibliography: note cards, n.d. (Box 61)
  - Unidentified bibliography: note cards, n.d. (Box 61)
- Series 6. Appointment books / Calendars
  - Executive's data book, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Executive's data book, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Saturday Review executive's desk diary, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Flores, Flowers agenda, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Venezuela calendario-agenda, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Venezuela calendario-agenda, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Venezuela calendario-agenda, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Week-at-a-glance, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Shell desk diary, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Week-at-a-glance, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Executive planner, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Week-at-a-glance, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - American Express appointment book, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - American Express appointment book, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - American Express appointment book, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - American Express appointment book, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Weekly appointment book, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Month-at-a-glance appointment book, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Month-at-a-glance appointment book, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Ansel Adams calendar, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Month-at-a-glance appointment book, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Week-at-a-glance appointment book, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Week-at-a-glance appointment book, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - UNICEF engagement calendar, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - A literary companion engagement calendar, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Chile ' 96 agenda fotográfica, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Series 7. Conferences, Symposia, Lectures
  - Biblioteca Nacional, Santiago, Chile, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - California Institute of International Studies conference (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - California State University, Dominguez Hills. Doctora Juana Aranciba (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Celebration o Chilean Arts, Culture, and Literature, 1999 Nov. 10-21 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Women Writers 1999 Nov. 10-21 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Congreso de la Nueva Narrativa Hispanoamericana, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Congreso Internacional de Literatura Iberoamericana (XIII) (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Congreso Internacional Jose Saramago (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Congreso Internacional Sobre Revistas de Critica Literaria (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - La Critica Literaria en Latinoamericana, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Donald Stoke's memorial 1988 July 17 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Encuentro de Escritores Americanos (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Encuentro de Intelectuales por la Soberania de los Pueblos de Nuestra America (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Encuentro Internacional Bienal de Capitulos Academia Iberoamericana de la Poesia (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Encuentro Latinoamericano de Escritores, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Encuentro Poetico-Musical con Fernando Alegria (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Feria Internacional del Libro de Santiago (14a) (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Fiesta 1996 Sept. 18 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - From Frei and Frei, 1997 Apr. 24-26 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Fromm Institute 1990 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Instituto Internacional de Literatura Iberoamericana 1959 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Inter-American Committee, Inc. First symposium [1 of 2] (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Inter-American Committee, Inc. First symposium [2 of 2] (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Inter-American Committee, Inc. Second symposium (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - International Seminar of Distinguished Scholar of Hispanic letters, 1998 July 13-17 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Latin American Studies Association Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Latinoamerica Viva (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Library of Congress reading: La novela chilena en el exilio exterior, 1992 Apr. 30 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Literatura Juvenil para las Americas, 1979 Oct. 15-19 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Los Escritores Tienen La Palabra: conference (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Madison Conference on Chile (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Modern Languages Association Convention 1975 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Pablo Neruda: a symposium, 1974 Nov. 21-23 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Philological Association of the Pacific Coast annual meeting, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Philological Association of the Pacific Coast annual meeting, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Primer Encuentro de Escritores, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Rocky Mountain Council on Latin American Studies, 1995 Mar. 5-9 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Seminario Internacional de Estudios Literarios 1994 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Simposio en conmemoración del LXXX aniversario de Pablo Neruda, 1984 Sept. 21-22 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Spanish Civil War Semicentennial, 1986 May 18-24 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Symposio Internacional de Literatura, 1995 Aug. 14-18 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Whose Whitman?, Fresno, 1992 Mar. 20-22 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Whitman in Spanish Translations, Iowa, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - University of Iowa. Walt and the World: the Obermann Seminar, 1992 Mar. 30-31 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Escuela Internacional de Verano: conference schedule, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Series 8. Consular Papers
  - Consular correspondence, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Consular correspondence, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Consular correspondence, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Consular correspondence, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Consular correspondence, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Consular correspondence, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Consular correspondence, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Consular correspondence, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Communicaciones - Cultura 1971 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Consular correspondence [1 of 4], 1972 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Consular correspondence [2 of 4], 1972 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Consular correspondence [3 of 4], 1972 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Consular correspondence [4 of 4], 1972 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Consular correspondence, 1973 - 1974 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Memoranda Embajador [1 of 2] (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Memoranda Embajador [2 of 2] (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores. Circulares (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Chile. Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores. Circulares (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Recibos = Receipts (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Actividades personales del Consejero: conferencias, charles, etc. = Personal activities of the Counselor: conferences, talks, etc., 1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Actividades en Embajada y Universidades = Activities in the Embassy and Universities [1 of 2] 1971 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Actividades en Embajada y Universidades = Activities in the Embassy and Universities [2 of 2] 1971 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Consular seal, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Series 9. Legal files
  - Chile. Direccion de Biblioteca, Archivos, y Museos. Permission to take artwork out of Chile (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Driver's License revoation, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Durable Power of Attorney (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Forcible medication and restraint (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Departamento. Victoria Subercaseaux 337, Dept. 52 y 53 [re: sale of apartment] (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Escritura a La Reina y plano de subdivision (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Banco de Chile, Parcela de La Reina, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Especificaciones tecnicas y presupuesto de ejecución, Parcela de La Reina, 1989 Dec. (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Venta: Parcela de La Reina: documentos (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Protocolización mandato y autorización Alegria A., Fernando y otra á Alegria A., Santiago, 1974 Apr. 15 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Fredman, Stephen: agent's contract (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Stuart Hyatt. Movie rights to Horse Journals by Fernando Alegria (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Series 10. Teaching materials
  - Universidad de Chile: correspondence (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Universidad of California, Berkeley: correspondence (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Universidad of California, Berkeley: historia personal de Alegria = Alegria's personal history [1 of 2] (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Universidad of California, Berkeley: historia personal de Alegria = Alegria's personal history [2 of 2] (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Universidad of California, Berkeley: University bulletin (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University. Correspondence with University (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University. Administrative documents (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University. Annual faculty reports, 1973-1983 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University. Annual salary listings, 1976-1990 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University. Alegria's letterhead (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program. Spanish 001, 1992 Fall (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program. Spanish 001: Magic realism: course reader, 1992 Fall (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program. Spanish 001: Magic realism: student papers, 1992 Fall (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program. Spanish 002: Latin American winner of the Nobel Prize in Literature I (SPN 002) (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program. Spanish 002B: Latin American Literature, 1995-1996 Winter (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program. HS179: Spanish Civil War, 1991 Fall (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Stanford University. Continuing Studies Program. HS179: Spanish Civil War, 1991 Fall (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Student and faculty directories (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. La familia Parra (SP 375), 1992 Spring (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. La familia Parra (SP 375): course reader, 1992 Spring (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. La familia Parra (SP 375): student papers, 1992 Spring (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Garcia Marquez seminario (SP 352), 1986 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Garcia Marquez seminario (SP 352), 1986 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Inventing history, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Inventing history: Reasons of state, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Latin American literature and social development, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Narrativa breve de Mexico, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. El otoño del patriarca: seminario, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Poetry class, 1996 Spring (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Latin American poetry song: final essays, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Spanish 306, 1983 Fall (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Ursula Welz: proposal for doctoral dissertation, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Kimberley Ford: graduate study application (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University. Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese. Marjorie Agosin: Independent research: Literatura chilena en el exilio (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University. Center for Latin American Studies talks (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University. Overseas Studies Program (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Stanford University. Overseas Studies Program, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University. Overseas Studies Program: Santiago, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Stanford University. Wallace Stegner Fellowship: Penelope Duckworth application package (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Stanford University. Correspondence with Victor Farias re: possibly teaching at Stanford University (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Stonybrook. Latin American cultural development (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Texas Christian University. Correspondence with University, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Texas Christian University. Promotional booklet (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Universidad Nacional Mayor de San Marcos: correspondence (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Whitman and Neruda: a syllabus n.d., 1 v. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous class notes n.d. (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Series 11. Photographs
  - Subseries A. Fernando Alegria
    - Fernando Alegria, 1920 - 1929 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1940 - 1949 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1950 - 1959 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Fernando Alegria / Juris Bodnar 1950 - 1959 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1960 - 1969 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1960 - 1969 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1960 - 1969 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Fernando Alegria: photographs / by Benjamin D. Lourie, 1960 - 1969 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1970 - 1979 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1970 - 1979 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Fernando Alegria with [Ricardo Gullon ? ] and others, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1980 - 1989 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1980 - 1989 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1980 - 1989 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1980 / Andres [Reeks?], photographer, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Fernando Alegria: photographs / by Alejandro Stuart, [198-] (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Fernando Alegria, 1990 - 1999 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Fernando Alegria with [Inti-Illimani?], [199-] (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Fernando Alegria, n.d., 9 slides; 35 mm. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Doctorate ceremonies for Fernando Alegria, University of San Marcos, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Fernando Alegria at cocktail party, [196-] (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Fernando Alegria on trip to [South America], 1972 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Fernando Alegria at cocktail parties, 1980 - 1989 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Fernando Alegria at Coyoacan, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Fernando and Carmen Alegria with friends at Valparaiso, Chile, Dia de los Pescaderos, [197-] (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Fernando Alegria seated at patio, n.d., 10 photographs: b & w; 9 x 12 cm. + 3 photographs: b & w; 8 x 8 cm. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Fernando Alegria at barbeque with Pablo Neruda, [197-] (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Fernando Alegria with Fernando Imabal at Golden Gate Park, 1960 Apr. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Fernando Alegria with friend, n.d., 3 photographs: col.; 9 x 12 cm. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Fernando Alegria with others, 1970 - 1989 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Fernando Alegria with others, 1990 - 1999, 4 photographs: col.; 10 x 16 cm. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Fernando Alegria with others, Boston, Massachusetts, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Fernando Alegria with unidentified cleric [Brother Antoninus?], n.d., 41 photographs: b & w; 8 x 8 cm. (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Fernando Alegria with unidentified cleric [Brother Antoninus?], n.d., 24 negatives: b & w; 6 x 6 cm. (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Alegria giving lecture, n.d., 4 photographs: b & w; mounted (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Fernando Alegria: photograph / Chris Felver, ca. 198-, 1 photographs: b & w (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Fernando Alegria: photograph, ca. [198-] (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B. Family and Friends
    - Alegria, Carmen (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Fernando Alegria's [father?], 2 photographs: b & w; 8 x 12 cm. (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Fernando Alegria with his [mother?] (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Alegria, Santiago (brother) (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Fernando Alegria's children (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Family photographs, ca. 1901 - 1959 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Family photographs, 1960 - 1969 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Family photographs, ca. 1973 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Family photographs, 1974 Feb. 27 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Family photographs, 1978 - 1989 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Family photographs, ca. 1991 Oct. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Family photographs [in Chile], [199-] (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Family and friends, 1960 - 1969 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Family and friends, 1970 - 1979 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Family and friends, 1980 - 1989 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Family and friends, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Family and friends, 1990 - 1999 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Family and friends, 1990 - 1999 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Family and friends, 1990 - 1999 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Family and friends, n.d., 12 negatives: b & w; 35 mm. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Trip to Peru, ca. 1965 June, 64 photographs: b & w + negatives: b & w; Minox PX format (Box 74, Folder 13)